7/23/2018 myFirstResume.html

Ryosuke Hujisawa

Full-Stack Developer

interview@off.tokyo Vancouver, BC 36-668-4441

Personal Profile

I have been working for a Full-Stack Developer for 5 years, with my most recent experience being a web developer. My strong point is the "patient". I had a experienced working with a one company on a long-term basis. I want to long-term basis with you.

Work Experience

Apple Corporation Ad inc (2013 ~ 2018) EXPERIENCE-1 (iOS Developer)

January 2013 - December 2014

• Familiarity with Swift4, perfect(Server-side Swift), Realm, React Native, or any mobile app development. AdMob Mobile Ads Operation

EXPERIENCE-2 (Web Developer)

February 2015 - December 2017

- Practical understanding of Javascript (ES6, Node.js), HTML5 and CSS, Bootstrap, AJAX, JQuery, and Experienced PHP MAMP and WordPress.
- Experience deploying Applications to AWS, Heroku and experience with one or more database systems MySQL

EXPERIENCE-3 (Data Science Developer)

January 2018 - June 2018

• Experience Server application development with Python, Django.

PERSONAL SIDE ROJECT

 $(2013 \sim 2018)$

Wordtranslate(Translation of sentences into words)

January 2013 - December 2014

Bootstrap, PHP, AWS and Python

Wesound(Music material share like SoundCloud)

February 2015 - December 2017

WordPress, HTML5 and CSS, JQuery, MySQL, PHP, AWS

Portfolio(My self-introduction site)

January 2018 - June 2018

· Bootstrap, GitHub

World Clock(Specify time and convert)

January 2018 - June 2018

· Server-side Swift - Perfect, ubuntu, HTML5, CSS3

Education

 $(2012 \sim 2017)$

Horikoshi High School

March 2012- April 2015

· General high school, Science course major

Senshu University Faculty of Computer Science

(Night school for working adult student) March 2015 - April 2017

• A technology foundation of information and computation, Analysis and research of compiler structure, Basic programming with C language

Key Skills

 $(1997 \sim 2018)$

Laugh often Love much Passion for work

Dream Big Relationship Music is always